Alright guys, it's time. I'm gonna share
with you
all the AI loops that I use.
Maybe not all, maybe just three to
begin with, but AI loops I use
for work to help grow revenues faster.
Because all this stuff, all this talk
about  Oh, you know, I use
this stuff to  make it my
chief of staff.  Or  you
use AI like you use ChatGPT. That's
not interesting. What's interesting is if it
helps you grow your business faster. And
for whatever reason,
still to this day, it's July 9th
right now, still people are not really
talking about it. I don't understand. Call
these content creators right now. How are
you not talking about how it makes
r  how it makes revenue for
your business? Oh, well. Maybe it's okay,
people are different stages. Maybe they don't
have a business, right? Uh maybe they're
solo, which is totally fine too. But
I'm gonna show you real life
implementation  um of these AI loops
because people have been talking about loops
for a while. But what's interesting to
me is uh yesterday a recruiter reached
out to me, like uh like someone
that that that has like a placement
recruiter  and And he's like, yeah,
you know, I use AI for for
sourcing talent and all. I was like,
oh great, fantastic. What are the loops
that you build and how did you
build them? And he's like, well, you
know, it's not like from a machine
learning perspective, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
He's writes like four paragraphs, wall of
text, and I'm just like, this guy's
no idea what he's talking about. Okay.
So I'm gonna first do a refresher
on what a loop is  and
how it's a little different than what
an agent is or what a slash
goal command is.  Um and if
you stay till the end, we'll even
share with you the loop's creator skill.
And you know what? I'll
I'll tell you where to go get
it afterwards.  Even better, because we
have even more skills for you there.
So you're gonna have to stay until
the end for that. And I might
forget, Max, you might have to remind
me, or someone might have to remind
me in chat.  But drop in
chat right now where you're coming from
from in the world.  And
uh we're gonna get started here.
And uh let's first go through a
recap of what a what a loop
is, okay? So I I actually have
this nice diagram for you all. So
I  share my screen. Okay.
Okay, so this is the difference between
an agent versus a loop. Everyone's talking
about loops right now, right? So again,
loop agent has there's there's
prompts that you can have. A lot
of people, they're not even using prompts
anymore. They're too good for prompts, right?
Or a slash goal command where
you tell it to do something and
it does it for an extended period
of time. For example, right now, and
I'll I'll show you in a little
bit, I've had a slash goal command
running for the last
I think the last sixty hours or
so, something like that, it's still running
right now.  Um, and you can
use different tools. You can have different
connectors, right? So you can connect in
your CRM, you can connect in your
revenue intelligence, uh like your your phone
calls, you can connect your different project
management tools. Like the more tools that
you have, the more helpful your agent
becomes, like Hermes, for example.  Um,
or and and you can also have
answers and artifacts in there. So you
can have PDFs, you can have documentation,
and and this is good. Agents are
really good, don't get me wrong. And
and I I use a lot was
using my agents this morning. They're really
good, they're extremely helpful. Now loops
on the other hand, the main difference,
because when people are talking about loops,
everyone's like, oh, you know, the creator
of Claude Code, the creator of the
creator of uh open clause, oh yeah,
you it's all about loops, all about
loops. And then like everyone's talking about
it, but nobody's explaining it well. And
then through  a lot of studying
over the next, I don't know, one
to two weeks, I say a lot
of studying, really just me kind of
thinking about it every day. Um not
a lot of studying, but  I
realized the main difference is that a
loop is able to,  it's able
to record the learnings and it's able
to compound on those learnings, right? People
talk about recursive self-improvement. But in my
mind, a loop is something that is
able to,  it's able to
look at what the target state is.
So I I've what I what the
example I like to use here is
that let's say you know you're you
want all of the sites,  all
the pages on your site to be
50 milliseconds.  Okay, that's a target
state that you're defining. Well, maybe then
you want your loop to be able
to observe the current state. So you
want to be able to see what
the base level is at. So maybe
the base level is 150 milliseconds. Okay.
So the gap, the gap right now
is 150 minus 50 equals 100, right?
So 100 milliseconds is the gap. And
then then the loop will continue to
work. And you can have a slash
goal inside of a loop, right? And
you can have it, you know, run
for an extended period of time. Um,
and then you can you can learn,
stop, or escalate. So this is what
we're talking about here. We we want
to build operating leverage.  And um,
I don't think enough people are talking
about it in in this way. And
so that's why I decided to make
a skill that's tied to it.
And um, I workshopped this a little
bit, I shared a lot of these
X articles. Um, I looked at what
other people were doing with their loops,
and I made my own skill with
it, and then I realized that. I'm
like, okay, well if you're gonna if
you're gonna record the state and you're
gonna record the learnings, like where do
you store all that?  Um and
so I'm like, can we just I
was just talking to my Hermes making
this loops creator skill. I'm like
Do we just put it in a
repo? It's like, yeah, repo's fine. I'm
like, okay, we're just gonna put it
in a repo then. So  um
at the end of this, I will
share with you where to get the
uh loops creator skill that we have
and also the repo template  and
a whole host of all of our
other skills. It's it's basically a skills
marketplace, okay?  So we'll we'll get
to that in a little bit, but
I just want to share this with
you all in terms of what an
agent versus a loop looks like. Again,
a loop is something that can create
operating leverage and an agent's good for
bounded execution. So that's what I would
say.  And I'm gonna quickly look
at where you guys.
So let's see, we Montreal, Sean, we
got Pinehurst, North Carolina. We've got Austin,
Texas. We've got Spokane. Amazing.
Thank you for that, Bob. I'll take
that as well. We got Minnesota. Bill
from Phoenix. Okay, great. ah Orlando,
Florida. Okay, awesome. So um, and I'll
answer you, keep asking questions as we
go because I can see questions coming
in from YouTube. I see questions coming
in from the webinar as well. Um,
Kevin, one of our ClickFlow customers coming
in as well. Um, by the way,
one thing, one other thing I'll say.
So Kevin is a user of one
of our products called ClickFlow.  ClickFlow
is an AEO SEO tool and there's
an API for it. There's an API
and MCP. Guess what? When you think
about your agents over here, when you
think about connecting tools, you can connect
like let's say you're using an SEO
tool like HRES. You can use the
API there or Semrush. And then you
can use Clickflow or you can connect
in with your Google Analytics for you
can connect it in with your Google
Search Console. You can connect it in
with the like for for for me
when I when I talk to um
you know Max on this call over
here. I'm like, dude, I talk about
so much every single week  and
there's there's gotta be at least three
or four content spikes that should become
content on our on our website for
AEO and SEO purposes and it should
draft it out. And then using my
friend's company,  um, my friend has
a bunch of WordPress businesses. One of
them is called WP Vibe. So if
you're using WordPress, there's a WordPress MCP
there. So imagine it's looking at all
the content that I'm I'm putting out
there. It's looking at what's genuinely differentiated.
And then it'll use something like an
HRS to look at hey, like is
this keyword, are these are these topics
actually trending upwards? Are they not? Um
are these perhaps content gaps that we
should attack? Then you can use a
content writer like a ClickFlop. By the
it's free. You can use the the
API MCP for free for a little
bit, test it out, see if you
like it. And then what you could
do is you can use an MCP
with WordPress and then push it over
there, draft it. I wouldn't say just
let it yellow and and let it
do its thing, but that's an example
of an agent that runs. Now.
What I'm gonna move to next is
I'm gonna show you the loop that
keeps this going. Cause the problem right
now is I'm talking about an agent
here, because the the problem with an
agent, you gotta keep running it over
and over. It doesn't learn. You gotta
keep repeating it. And it's like, that's
like a solid B player, you know?
A B player employee is like, you
gotta tell them what to do, right?
An A player employee is like they
just solve the problem and then they
compound and they keep learning.  I
was actually on a stand-up call about
30 minutes ago and I was talking
to it to to one of our
designers, and I was like,
Who like you you're you're really good
at AI right now? Who had who
taught you all this stuff, right? And
I wasn't expecting him to say me
at all.
Him. He taught him all this stuff.
Good people don't need to be told
this, right? And so I I would
just encourage you all to say this.
Cause I had a friend call the
other day. She's like, every day I
get strong with this stuff, I my
my tolerance for BS goes lower and
lower. And you all should feel the
same. So if you're working on a
company right now and you find that
there's a lot of inertia around you,
go find another company, right? And
and like but but if you're running
a company right now and there's there's
a lot of that BS around you,
you gotta drop the hammer, right?
Um and you can drop the
hammer in a nice way, but like
I th that's all I'm saying. So
I digress. Let me show you the
AEO loop here. This is the first
loop that I'm gonna show you.
Um and John, maybe I can tie
this into CLOD  and uh Uber
suggests MCP.  Um, you know,
we'll come to that in a second.
So I'm I'm seeing Neil uh later
today. We're gonna be recording marketing school
too, by the way. So let me
move my share to my codex. So
codex is my daily driver. Um
I like codex, even though I have
Cloud code as well. And so I
think you all can see this. Okay,
great. So this is my GEO
AEO loop. Okay.  And uh maybe
I'll I'll I'll put this in the
area. The the uh we're gonna have
a section for loops for that that
um skills marketplace I'm gonna show you
as well.  Um but
the way I see  the way
this works right now, like this is
working for a very long time. All
this yeah, I'm gonna save watch.
Hey, I'm doing a webinar right now.
Can you explain in one sentence what
this actually does and how high leverage
this is on a scale of one
to one hundred?  And that's a
little thing, while while this thinks too,
by the way, I always like to
ask the question. I like I want
my AI to push back on me.
I want it to be my thought
partner. So one through one hundred, like
what like how high leverage is this?
I want to know how genuinely differentiated
is this, or is this just like
a like a like a BSD? And
oftentimes I'll share I'll be sharing my
whatever I'm reading on X. I'm just
constantly sharing it to my Hermes. Or
maybe sometimes I'm sharing it to my
codex over here.
So what does it say? Look, guys,
I don't even have to work. I
just
This turns SEO and AEO work into
an operating loop that finds page opportunities,
drafts or updates content, quality checks it,
routes it for human approval, and then
tracks results over time. Leverage 92 out
of 100 if we connect it cleanly
to publishing and analytics feedback.  How
does it work in one sentence? What
connectors does it have? Right? So
I'm gonna keep working here. So, what
I'm actually doing right now as I'm
going back and forth, look at all
this other crap I have on the
left sidebar. So every day as a
business owner, I think about all the
bottlenecks. And if you guys have read
the book, The Goal, I highly recommend
that you read it. So, and and
I highly recommend that you push your
team to read it too, at least
your A players, because then they will
understand what the theory of constraints are.
Because every business has constraints. Always. Every
business has constraints, right? So what does
it do here? It pulls signals from
ClickFlow.  HRS brand radar. HRS is
a great MCP API, by the way.
Um G A So Google Analytics
4, Google Search Console, Hermes Content Ingester.
So Max here in the knows
that we have this Hermes content ingester
um where it's it's pulling my content
every single week. And local site and
template evidence turns them into update, uh
consolidate, delete, net new page actions, drafts
the work, runs QA, stops for human
approval, then tracks 714 30-day results.
Okay, well, how is this a real
loop?  And how did the loops
creator actually help build this?
And how helpful was it?  So
think about this.
If you're running this for AEO and
SU and it's running every single week,
imagine if it's pumping out fifty pages
for you and then you have an
editor that's spot checking these and maybe
you approve 20 of them. So you
have a 20 new ones coming per
week. Or maybe if you have a
travel website and you have a lot
of pages on your travel website, you
can go a lot more aggressive if
you want to, right? Um and then
you can probably have a loop that
that's spending time just focused on AEO
optimizations. Do you have an FAQ? How's
your schema markup doing, right? Um all
all these things. Oh, you can probably
s like  all the things that
you do right now are are a
loop.
Like
Come on. Like if you're not setting
these up right now,
you are, I think you're wasting time
in terms of how you work. So
excuse me.
So it is a real loop because
each run has state, evidence, scoring, action
decisions, human gaze, and follow-up measurement, observe
page content signals, choose next URL action,
draft or prepare packet, evaluate quality, duplicate
uh template, duplicate template fit, ask for
approval. Guess what?  If your SEO
agency or your SEO sucks, fire all
of them. You don't need them anymore,
right? I'm sorry. You don't need the
ones that aren't good. You need the
ones that are good to run. You
need the ones that are good to
run this stuff. You need the ones
that understand how to compound themselves. You
need to have the ones that understand
how to how to create leverage
um out of their out of their
lives, right? Like honestly, if if I
were like uh if I were coming
out of college right now, I'd be
having uh the time of my life
because
because I played a lot of games
growing up.  And I'm like, dude,
like
I think I'm gonna be a failure.
Like this is when I was a
kid, by the I'm like, man, I
think I'm gonna be a failure. Cause
like all I all I want to
do is play games. But
this feels like a video game. And
actually, Max, people can't hear you, but
like, Max, does this kind of feel
like a video game like  right
now for you? I'm gonna see what
Max says. Go ahead.
Max says for sure, I don't know
if he's just appeasing me, but
um, I think I think he's actually
telling the truth.  And um
when life feels like a video game
to you and you wake up, you
look forward to it. Right? And you
and and then you realize that you
only want to hire people that that
work like this. Okay. So anyway, all
that to say, we're gonna come back
to this in a little bit, but
my my point is you guys can
all see this. Like it doesn't have
to be an AEO or SEO thing.
How does this apply to social media?
Because I'm sure the the all of
you watching this right now, the
the wheel should be turning in your
head. How can I make this work?
Like, what is the most annoying thing
right now that I can make into
a loop? Now I'm gonna move to
the next one to give you some
more ideas. I have a CRO loop
over here, okay?
So  This CRO loop, okay, so
like,
what does this do in one sentence?
And tell me how it's a real
loop, and tell me what connectors it
has, and tell me how high leverage
this is on a scale of one
to one hundred. You guys see how
I'm doing that? Same thing over and
over. In fact, go to YouTube later,
take the transcript from this video, okay?
And just say, hey, how do I
skillify everything Eric is talking about? That's
how lazy you can be now. Be
smart, but be lazy. All right. So
J uh Jack says, yeah, weekly scan
my website traffic.
What's the workflow for making the SEO
loop? Well, you gotta stay till the
end for that because we will share
the repository,
but also the marketplace and where you
can get our skills and our loops.
All right. So uh let's see, let's
see.
Where do you get the results of
your codex loop? So  um
Basically the way this works right now
is you can see that there's a
little clock next to this thing. You
can do the same thing in cloud
code as well. You can do the
same thing with your Hermes. You can
set up cron jobs and you can
have the desktop app and you can
you can look at where all your
skills and where your cron jobs are.
If you're using Hermes, I highly recommend
using the desktop app. Um like for
someone like me, I I get lost
a lot because there's just I have
so many things running in parallel. Um
but this is a real CRO loop
because it runs scheduled live site and
GA4 readbacks, records state artifacts, compares conversion
rate against baseline and target decision roles.
And escalates keep win lose iterate. Connectors
are GA4 service count, public site checks,
and codecs, cron local repo, plus Vercell
rollback contacts when approved.  Um, because
it turns so this is 86 out
of 100 leverage because it turns home
page CRO into a repeatable decision system,
but still lacks randomized A B sm
Okay, watch. So I don't like an
86, right?
Because when you're Asian, an 86 is
considered an F, okay? So
I want you to  put together
a I want you to do a
UX review on this  and I
want you to put together a team
of uh expert I'm gonna put
I want you to put together an
expert panel of UX  um
UX UI people  that are best
in class and also conversion rate optimization
people that are best in class to
figure out what we need to do
to improve this to make this a
95 plus. So I want you to
continue to score this until it becomes
95 plus, and then  in one
sentence, tell me the changes that you
would make.  Um and let's go
from there.
So what I'm doing over here is
I'm saying, Oh, what did I say?
I want
I want you to do a UX
review. So that is pulled from Gary
Tan's. Uh he has G-Brain and G
stack. So he has CEO review, UX
review, finance review, like all these different
reviews that you can run. So these
are skills that I'm pulling in here.
Uh and I have look, look, look,
look, three skills. I didn't like I
forgot I had these. Okay. So there's
we like apparently we have an expert
panel one, we have a page CRO
one, and we have a design review
skills as lenses. And uh we're just
gonna let this work, okay? But my
point here is that every single week,
this is gonna run a new test.
And it knows the baseline number is
1.80% right now on the convergent rate
for singlebrain.com. Um, and I said, hey,
just raise it, raise it by 30%
in the next four weeks. This is
something that was a full-time job before,
right?  In terms of having someone
that's on top of your CRO. Not
anymore. Same thing with my AEO SUPs.
Okay, not only is it scanning content
ingesters, it's scanning my website too, it's
scanning for opportunities. Maybe it's also scanning
the web too. You can use you
can
You can sorry about that. Um, you
can also combine that with other skills.
Like uh Matt um  Matt Van
Horn has this um
it's called last 30 days, and you
guys can look it up, but but
the last 30 day skills is really
good because you can just say, hey,
last use the last 30 day skills
to look at what's trending in marketing
or AI or business. And in fact,
I use that today for marketing school
because I'm recording in in a bit
with Neil,  and um, it came
up with a with some pretty good
ideas. In fact, I'll show you those
I  those ideas in a moment.
Um
And let's see it, let's see what's
happening over here.
That it answered me a little too
quickly, so we'll see what happens. So
let me pull up marking school for
today. I'm gonna show you the topics
that it came up with. Um, and
this is in fact something I can
make into a loop too.  Um,
if if if I show here, let
me just share my screen real quick.
I'm gonna move
and then maybe I'll answer some questions
as we go along. So let's move
over here. Okay, great.
So let's see. Okay,
notice today is
the 9th  of July.
All this  is from the last
30 day skill. Okay? So
sorry guys, I don't know why the
coughing is coming out now, but
um, your attribution dashboard is lying. Cold
email reply rates are collapsing. LinkedIn wants
you to own, uh wants to own
B2B creator discovery. Software is becoming marketing.
Okay, that's pretty good. Your brand is
invisible in AI search. Okay, guess what?
This is a  I think they
gave me 10 to 10 ideas, 15
ideas, something like that. And then I
gave some ideas here too. And I
said, hey, I threw in some ideas,
also add in the hook. Uh I
want you to add in the hooks
here and add in the hooks. What
if half half of companies need new
CEOs? So ex Google president, 50% of
companies will need new leadership. 95% of
AI transformations failing. Why are 95% of
AI transformation? Okay, this is all good.
Because then now I don't need to
think about what are the hooks I'm
gonna have for short form content. Okay.
I don't need to think about what's
interesting because last 30 days we'll look
it'll look at the entire internet and
look at what's interesting.  Guess what?
I can plug that into my
So you just you're every single week,
it's not like you're done working, you're
constantly adding more and more to the
loops that you have, and you're also
probably deprecating the loops that don't make
any sense to keep. Um and but
like if you continually do that, and
this is why this is how we
we teach our people internally, like how
like uh we we do this
pod of one apprenticeship right now. And
I'm gonna come back to um Codex
in a second, but we do this
pod of one apprenticeship. Why do we
do this? It's where I'm doing like
a group training with the people who
are AI pilled.  Um, most most
people are AI pilled, I'd say, in
that meeting. And then um
we are trying to make one person,
we're trying to give one person the
ability to do 10 different things. And
so a week ago, it was more
so about building the right skills, having
someone else use the skill and then
make a loom around it to kind
of verify it. And so that's the
first piece.
But now we're moving on to loops.
So how do you  make a
loop?
How do you verify it?
Excuse me. Um, okay, so
that's that. That's how this works. But
hopefully you guys are seeing how all
this stuff you can actually actually daisy
chain them together.  And that that's
why it's very important to have a
skills marketplace as well.  Um, because
You wanna be able to share the
wealth. There's no sense in me doing
this all on my own if I
can't share this with my team and
I can't help my team get better.
It is actually a failure on my
part if I become way stronger and
my team becomes weak, like they don't
they don't get stronger. That means I'm
not a good leader, right? So as
much as possible, your job is to
bring the people who want to come
along and create the conditions for success.
And there's gonna be a contingent
of people that don't want to come
along and they're gonna self-select themselves out.
But that is the way the world
works. And um
I was  talking to a friend
of mine the other day, her her
business does about 14 million a year,
and she was like, you know.
Again, like every day I get stronger
with this stuff,
I my tolerance for BS becomes lower
and that's how you should feel. Okay.
So uh let me move over to
go back to codecs and then
um I'm gonna show you
Okay, so  specific ninety-five plus changes.
Okay, change the hero to the name,
uh to name the buyer and outcome
directly. For example, deploy manage AI revenue
agents for sale. Okay, great.  So
these are these are all the changes
it's recommending, and then these are things
that I might I might just let
it run uh next time. So like
let's just ask it. Like I'm actually
wondering what's gonna happen. So
okay, so what happens here? If if
your test this week succeeds.
then like what do you do next?
Or if it fails, then what do
you go next? What do you do
next? Like I'm on a webinar right
now and I'm I'm showing people how
this works. So kind of do do
a good explanation here in terms of
uh
explaining your logic in terms of
How would you lift our converge rates
by 30% in the next four weeks?
Okay. So while that works, I'm gonna
show you one more thing. This is
um, I'm gonna make this into a
loop, but this has been running for
the last two days and 14 hours.
Okay, so 60 hours.
This thing's been running for 60 hours.
It's a slash goal command. It's uh
um  it's building our talent
OS recruiting loop, right? And so
um let me just let me just
see what this is. Okay.
So I'm gonna you what I did
here. Bring the talent OS recruiting loops
up to date across  this documentation
over here. Um and then inventory completed
work, reconcile existing changes, implement, implement safe
local changes in order, validate what tests
and stop before external rights. Okay, what
does this do exactly?  With recruiting
right now, because recruiting is a big
bottleneck for us, because we only want
to hire AI pilled people. And by
the way, if you're AI pilled and
you're looking for a new gig and
you think you're that damn good, we
would like to talk. Just go to
singlegrain.com slash apply. Again, single grain.com slash
apply. So
looking at this over here,  um,
you know, some of the best people
that we've gotten have come through um
sourcing, okay?  And we want a
machine that can basically source through LinkedIn.
It can also um source through
emails as well.  Um, and it
will follow up. It'll also optimize the
messaging that it's sending to people. It'll
also look at the the the roles
that are we're prioritizing every single week
because it kind of changes for us
uh quite frequently.  So
Right now you can see the the
platforms that it's touching right now, it's
looking at Team Taylor, which is our
our ATS,
our um applicant tracking system. There's LinkedIn,
it'll look at JuiceBox, which is our
AI kind of sourcing tool, uh, Gmail,
and it'll look at other candidates that
we have. And it'll start to spot
patterns. And you want a system, a
recruiting system that continues to get better.
Guess what?  You no longer
have to pay all these contingency fees
with recruiters. Okay. You now have a
machine that can do this for you.
So like All this stuff that I'm
showing you right now, like if you're
a business owner right now, you can
see all the problems with your business
every single day. What's the highest leverage
problem that you can make into a
loop?  Every single day. And sometimes
it's better for you to just focus
on one loop for the rest of
the week.  Um, but I'm telling
you, man, like this is probably in
the last three, four weeks, once I
understood how loops work, this is one
of the highest leverage things that I
can do. And I love doing this
stuff. I'll tell you what I don't
like. I don't like dealing with pupil
problems, right? Like the A players on
the team don't have to worry about
anything 'cause they just all wanna get
better all the time. What I hate
dealing with  is  um, you
know,  oh, you know, I just
don't have enough time.
Oh, it's too hard, right? Um, I
don't know how to do it, right?
You have to put your foot down
as a leader and say, those excuses
might have worked  seven months ago,
not anymore, right? And you get what
you tolerate ultimately.  Um now I
get it. Some of you maybe maybe
you're newer leaders, but I'm telling you,
I used to care so much about
being liked and being a a a
nice leader.  Nope, nobody likes that.
That's weak. All right, so.
That's how this this is this is
building right now. So sometimes these these
loops take a while to build, again,
working for 60 hours.  Um, I'm
gonna show you  one more. I'm
gonna show you my Mr. Sue sponsorship
one, which I showed last time, but
I'm gonna show you how it's it's
getting better. And oh, actually, we have
this uh HubSpot um hygiene one over
here. Um, what this one is, it's
like looking for it's coming up with
suggestions on what to fix or update
from a hygiene standpoint in HubSpot. Right
now we're still having a human in
the loop review the changes that it's
recommending. Then once we iterate on it,
it's it's gonna become better. Cause some
of these things sometimes like you have
to,  as you're building these loops,
you have to still be the human
look giving it feedback. You have to
constantly be iterating with it. Otherwise, if
you just expect it to build it
all for you with with limited context,
you're gonna get garbage.
So that's that.
Oh, what else? Chat GT chat chat
GTM light loop handoff. Okay. This one's
cool.  Um
Max, I don't know if I said
you in this article, but  um
this article was written about so
this chat GTM thing. So I
I read about a guy at uh
he's the head of go to market
at Cursor.  And
You know, he's talking about how all
of his um sales reps will like
a brief every morning for the the
the calls that they're gonna get gonna
get involved with. Um and then also
it makes like a custom landing page
for all of the um the the
let's say the discovery calls that they're
about to have and so they can
go through that custom landing page. So
imagine when you get on a call
with um someone's doing a demo with
you and they they show you a
custom landing page,  um, and it's
like it's clearly like set up just
for you and they they went it
looks like they went through the time
and effort to do that. How much
more likely are you to win that
deal? It's gonna go up significantly, right?
conversion rate's gonna go up significantly because
it shows that you went above and
beyond. And so he does that. He
preps people before the call, after, and
he's he's made all these things. Nobody
asked him to do this at Cursor.
So  this guy's name is George.
And I didn't realize this afterwards, I'm
like, wait, his name looks familiar. Guess
what? This guy went to my high
school and he's a valedictorian. He's much
younger than me. Um he worked my
for my friend's company for a little
bit. Um my friend's ha has uh
fun with Jake Paul.  Um and
I I think he does some business
with Logan Paul as well, too.
Um but my friend Jeff, you know,
hired this guy before and then now
he now now he's uh he's at
he's at this company, right? And so
um I'm just looking, I'm like,
you know what? I might just reach
out to him, but
What's easier right now is I just
took the post itself. Hey, which which
repo does it make sense to build
this into uh into a loop using
the loops creator? You see how lazy
I am? I have a loops creator
skill. I have an article that I
like, and I'm like, hey, we might
have repos that are related to this.
In fact, I know there are as
it relates to sales. I want to
build out what he's talking about as
it relates to what we're doing on
the sales side. So
it's almost like those of you that
follow basketball, I'm like,  I'm trying
to be this point guard where I'm
just kind of like creating these little
loops, maybe getting them 60. 70, 80%
there, I'm prototyping them. And then once
I feel good about it, then I
can hand it off. And so
I think the job of the founder
or like a leader now is
you're becoming this uh this this point
guard where you're distributing the ball quite
a bit. And even when we talk
to clients on the single brain side,
where we do these implementations for clients,
uh these these managed revenue agents,
um, it's
It it's a very collaborative call, um,
because everyone wants to do this stuff,
but sometimes they just need a little
direction, right? And so um all that
to say is like, you know, once
you start to show people how to
do this, like we work with other
founders that um we show them how
lazy we are being with this,
um, you know,  it it just
basically becomes a drug. So I'll leave
it at that. So
I think I have
I'll show one more and then maybe
I'll answer some questions here. So my
um  I showed you guys this
one last time, but I have this
Mr. Sue sponsorship one. Okay. So
um I have no idea what it's
doing right now.
Okay.
Here's here's what I'll say.  I
have this loop that basically handles my
sponsorships that come in for my YouTube
or my podcast. And basically it messages,
it replies to people saying Mr. Sue's
rate is $25,000 for one post. What
inevitably happens is they'll say, Oh,
sorry, we can't afford that. We just
want to do an affiliate deal. Our
budget's only $1,000.  It's $500, it's
$100, whatever it is exactly. And then
my thing became smarter and smarter
over time. It was like You know,
I'm sorry, Mr. Sue is very committed
right now. It's twenty five thousand dollars.
That's all he can do. Let let
us know if that works, right? So
it it like it draws a hard
line. And then  what started happening
afterwards is like was like people are
like, Okay, well if it's twenty five
thousand dollars, like,  um, you know,
how d like what are the usage
rights? W you know, what what's uh
You know,  uh, can we put
um yeah, usage rights, how long do
the usage rights last for it? Like
all this other stuff that I haven't
been thinking about. So  now what
happens is
this loop learns over time. It's running
every single day. So now when it
responds to people, it's like, hey, if
$25,000 works for you,  um, you
know,  uh our usage rights are
for one year and it's for this
and that. It's it starts adding in
all these things. And sometimes it'll check
with me if if I want to
have that in there, but it's adding
it in there and it's making the
responses better, it's making them more like
crisper because it's starting to see all
these patterns, right? And all this stuff
is Ultimately pattern recognition at the end
of the day. So um for me,
I don't want to deal with
having to deal with this. And I
also don't want to hand this off
to someone on my team to deal
with this. Like, in fact, like someone
on my team could be doing something
that that that's higher leverage. And so
again, you think about all the things
that annoy you right now, prioritize them,
and then start to think about how
you can loopify this stuff. So I'm
gonna start to answer some questions now,
and maybe I'll jump back to my
screen share if things pop up.
Um so  let's see,
I'm gonna answer some questions. Um
Let's see.
Okay. Let's start with the
what do we got? Uh uh okay,
not that one.
Uh I think you want to interact
with a child. Okay, got it. Do
we have a really you wanna just
throw a good one up, Max, if
you saw a good one?
So
John,  okay, you can throw one
up, but um I know John asked
one about having all this stuff hook
in with Claude Code or Uber Suggest
MCP. You totally can do that if
you want to.  Um  and
the next one would be from
Bob McIntosh, I think.
You got that one?
Okay. So this one, could you share
how you're framing to your team to
step up? I find that I think
my team is generally afraid AI will
take their job. I keep saying this
about 10X and productivity and not replacing
them. So  It's been seven months.
And here's what I'll say. The
last week of December,  I
I that's when Opus four five took
off and I went crazy on it.
That was that was my Christmas vacation,
basically, right?  Um and don't so
I I told everyone at the beginning
of the year, like everyone's gonna have
to be proficient with cloud code by
in six months. Now we've got all
this other stuff, right? We've got Hermes,
we've got um you know we've we've
got you know, we've got uh Fable
Five, we have op uh we we
have OpenAI, Chat GPD five point six
that just came out today, soul, right?
Um so
all that to say is that I
I've noticed that um the people that
that had that sense of agency, the
people that wanted to grow, the people
that have a good relationship with change
and they're very adaptable, they ate it
up. There needed to be not not
really any pushing. So we're doing all
these hackathons, we're doing all this, uh,
you know, we're doing these AI office
hours and things like that, we're meeting
with people one-on-one. Um, but I've just
found that you can't Change mindsets
that easily. People have to change it
on their own. I just f feel
that it's your job as a company
to set up the conditions for success.
And if people want to come along,
they can come along. The other thing
too is
if people have that mindset where they're
genuinely afraid of it.
My real question for that, Bob, is
like, how much time are they actually
putting into it right now? Right? Because
it's it's like there's  if they're
genuinely putting the time into it, they'll
realize that AI is is uh my
friend likes to say it's IA, it's
an intelligence amplifier. But if you're continually
afraid of it over and over and
over again, you're starting to become a
liability to the company. Um, because it's
no different like you can try all
this different framing. Oh, this is no
different than when the first internet when
the the internet first came out and
um  you know, people are a
lot faster because of the internet.
Um but this time the the the
only problem that I see with this
is that You have synthetic intelligence and
if you're compounding with the intelligence, the
gap's gonna get bigger and bigger. And
so  in my in my mind,
it's like, hey, you set up a
condition for success. If people want to
come along, they come along. But if
not, you have to be you you
have to you have to make decisions
for your company because if not, you're
gonna have two companies. You're gonna have
one company, one part of your company
that is super AI pilled and they're
having fun every single day and they're
they're working super hard. And you know,
I I just worry about their burnout
and I worry about You know, how
do we how do we pay these
people the best long term, right? That's
what I worry about. Um then there's
the other side where it's a different
c it's a different conversation. It's just
where you start to hear the things,
oh, it's too hard, I don't have
enough time, I'm overwhelmed, right? But
then it's like, what, what, but like
I'm working so hard right now and
I'm like, yes, it's my business, but
it I don't, I don't have like
I've certainly felt overwhelmed before. I don't
feel overwhelmed right now. In fact, it's
more so I can't stop myself from
working because it's so fun, right?
Um, so that's what I would say.
Like you, you you don't want to
have two cultures right now because that's
gonna cause culture clash and that's gonna
hold you back from achieving your goal.
So that was a longer answer to
what you're looking for, but um, I
hope that helps.
The next one.
Yeah, I think I answered that one
or you could you can throw it
up. That's fine.
Okay, so
where do I get the answers, the
results for my codec loop? So it
drops into codex and it would do
the same thing inside of your cloud
code as well. You can run CLI,
uh you you can you can run
this in the CLI as well.
Um you can also do this inside
of your Hermes agent or your open
call agent as well. So there's that.
Um  the workflow, let's see.
Let's see what else we got here.
Um I'll I'll scroll down. I forgot
that I can actually pull these up
myself too.  Um okay, so
let me pull this one up.
Let's show this one.
Oh, we need to show it from
longer. Let's do
20 seconds. Okay, here we go. So
Joe asks You shared how your AI
just pulled skills and ones you didn't
even remember you had. How are they
set up to go in and get
uh use them? It's a skill and
the skill says to go search uh
dojo or is okay. So here's what
it is.
A lot of my skills live in
my private repo in GitHub, and I
just connect my GitHub, my codex to
my GitHub, I connect my Hermes to
my GitHub, I connect my cloud code
to my GitHub, and that's how they
play together. And then I I I
did forget to tell you guys too.
If you guys want access to these
skills and um the the skills that
we have that we've shared publicly, I
think I uploaded like 150. fifty of
my own.  Um, but like these
loops, we're gonna be sharing these loops
in there as well. Just go to
skillsdojo.com. So I got to domain guys,
skillsdojo.com. Um I think there's a wait
list for it right now, but you
can sign up for it. But our
whole intention here is to have it
be public for everyone so you guys
can share your skills in there. And
maybe if you if I have a
skill like if if sorry, if I
find a skill that that you guys
have that I like, maybe I'll fork
it. So I might fork it and
then I might make it into my
own and I might use make it
for my my my own use cases.
But
wanna democratize these these skills out there
um  for everyone to to
use, right? And that that way it
it it makes it easier for you
to train your team. It eas it
makes it easier for your team to
to start to use loops as well.
So yeah, skillsdojo dot com.  Um
and then let's do um I'm
gonna pull this up this one up
from
Jack.
Where are you checking with all these
requests from your loop? Slack? My Slack
channels okay, don't do Slack. So if
you're gonna use loops, you're gonna set
up all these like cron jobs are
even hard to keep up with. Um,
I wouldn't use Slack for that. And
e like I even tried making a
cron job channel on Slack where where
Hermes would report in there or even
Codex would report in there. It's too
difficult.  So  I like again,
I like using the Hermes desktop app.
I like using Codex if you're gonna
build the loops in there. I like
using uh the Claude Code app because
it shows you, um, you can see
like it has a little like blue
thing. Hey, it's it's time for you
to come back to this or When
it's um when it's a recurring loop,
it'll show like a little clock and
it refreshes every single day, right? Or
every single week or however often it's
happening. So that makes it easier for
me to come back to it. And
I can see with my codex that
I have 84 scheduled things right now.
I probably can  cut 50% of
them. Um so you want to make
sure that you pare them down uh
every once in a while as well.
So in terms of cost, let me
pull this up. So in terms of
cost for running some of these loops,
like
Uh I ha I have API usage
if I need it. I have two
$200 codex  accounts like the ChatGPT
Max. So $200, $200.  Um
I have another $200 for Claud Code.
And then if I need to
switch to API usage, I will do
that. And so for like a Fable
5, for example, as of in three
days,  um, it's gonna be usage-based.
Let me cough real quick.
Okay, so
And then the other thing too is
is to consider is this. The reason
why I like using ChatGPT is because
they're so generous with their um
their plans. Because you basically get, for
200 bucks, you get $14,000 of usage.
That's like what it what it's mapped
out to be in terms of how
generous they are.  Um
And for 200 bucks with Claude, you
basically end up only getting 8,000. And
I I can actually tell the difference.
Um, and there was a month
where I paid about $14,000 on API
usage. So I know it feels just
about right. Like I can tell. And
so they can't subsidize forever, but if
you're watching this right now, you guys
should just go to town on it
and max out your usage every single
week. You can even set up
Like an eval loop  to run
through all the stuff that you have
running every single day. Um and to
basically try to try to do a
token burn before you um before your
your usage uh refreshes.  Um that's
what I would recommend. That's something that
that you can work on.  Um
so let's see, let's share this one
over here.
Um actually let's go to this one
real quick.
What AI tools are we using to
edit our podcasts? One,  I don't
have the best answer for you. I
can tell you. I could tell you
we're using Higgs field. I can tell
you for like the some of the
B-roll. I can tell you, I think
we're using D script a little bit
as well.
I can tell you that  um
there's other stuff I would like to
use. Oh, we use overlap for making
the um the mid-form clips that we
have that we we throw on to
X and LinkedIn, so that's been pretty
good for us.  Um
And then we uh we also use
Riverside. So you guys are on the
Riverside webinar right now. So Riverside's uh
been good. They have an MCP now.
Um  and yeah, so have
enjoyed Riverside as well. And then um
there's some AI tooling within Beehive, but
it's it's nothing too special right now,
that's what I'd say. And then
Joe says  You shared how your
AI  uh okay, yeah. We talked
about Skills Dojo. So go to the
Skills Dojo if you want the the
skills marketplace that we have. It's free.
Um and we're we're making like
a really public version um like next
week. But it's it's you should be
able to opt in uh immediately and
you should be able to get access
to um all these skills that we're
talking about, all these loops that we're
talking about.  Um so
let's see.
So Anthony says, I think what you're
seeing, uh, when you're seeing progress, it
becomes contagious, but there's meaningfully time cost
to get to the point with the
team moving things to get there in
in in my opinion. So  um,
yes and no,
it's not hard for me to, I
don't need to push the people that
understand this stuff.
If I need to push you, you're
probably not a fit to work at
my company, at least for me. And
like everyone's could be different. Um, the
best people don't need to be pushed.
And so you might be arguing, like,
well, you you it's not realistic for
you to have like the best people
across the board. And I would challenge
that because a lot of the people
that I'm talking to from a recruiting
standpoint right now that would love to
join the company,
they would join today
if we could get 'em today. And
like that's how like I the way
I'm looking at it now is like,
oh crap. we might actually need to
raise money. If I wanna get all
the people that I want to get
right now and also take care of
the current people that we have, we
need to raise money because we're building
we're building the services as software um
thing with single brain,  um, that
fits into single grain, right? And so
I don't know.  I I I
was thinking, Anthony, like in the beginning
of the year, okay, we're just gonna
train everyone up. And I've realized that
that's a fallacy. That y that you
think you can train people to be
motivated, that you can train people to,
you know, be relentless learners, to
to be biased to action. You you
can't You can't train that. That's a
mindset thing.  Um, there's certain things
that are much easier to train, there's
certain things that are much harder to
train. And I think w  if
you're gonna t if you're gonna make
a transformation like that, to become a
relentless learner, to to have a bias
to action, to make bold long-term bets,
to be super resilient, you have to
go through a lot in life and
there has to be
You have to be built a certain
way.  Um and so I thought
we could do that in the beginning
of the year. And I've just reason
realized this, like seven months into it,
you know, we've created conditions for success
and the ones that are they that
they had it all along, like it's
been no problem for them. It's
frustrating for me to see the peop
the other people that don't want to
take it on, um, because it
it makes me feel like I've failed
as a leader.  Um but You
at the end of the day, I
think about it, I'm like, well, i
i I I can't I can't make
them change their mindset. So long-winded answer
for you, but that that that's what
I would say, Anthony.  Um I
thought I could, you know, train it
all up.
Nope, can't do it. So
um  so there's that. Yeah. Anyway,
so  here's what I'll say.
Um go check out the go check
out the skills, Dojo.  Um, and
we're gonna continue to talk about loops
that we're building out. Um we're even
building out this game right now. Um
that maybe I'll show you guys for
a second and then um
we we posted this yesterday to Twitter
and actually did pretty well. And I
would say this.  Um
so
We have this image over here. So
Fable 5 just turned my company into
a video game. Now, is this live
right now? Like, no,  oh only
I'm testing it, right? So this here's
a lesson for you. So I made
this using Fable 5.  Um, you
have like a marketing hub, a product
lab, a sales engine, and you can
see if buildings are on fire, if
like you need to fix things for
these buildings. You can also set up
quests as well. You can see recent
activity. There's a leaderboard, there's active quests.
Um, and so you can give people
rewards. Or maybe if they get a
certain amount of XP, they can claim
it for rewards, right? But then you
can gamify your company.  Um, it
will also be make it very transparent
who's crushing. it and who needs help.
And for the people that need help,
maybe they truly need help and you
just need to help them.
Or maybe they don't they don't want
to work. That's a different problem, right?
Um, but we're gonna be testing
this internally to see what the engagement
looks like. And if you're gonna roll
things out, just make sure if you're
rolling out skills,  if you're rolling
out loops, that  other people at
least one other person is adopting it.
So there's it's not just a bunch
of theater. So  that's what I
would say. Um ah
And
you guys should drop in chat too,
by the way, as we as we
go through this. Like
what else you guys would like to
see? Because we're doing these w these
weekly webinars right now. We're also gonna
bring on guests. Like next I think
next week or the week after, we're
gonna um
We're gonna bring on Cody Cody Schneider
and he's gonna talk about how he
uses AI in the context of pay
media. And that's something that I don't
really talk about myself 'cause I'm more
of a SEO background. So let me
know what other topics would be interesting
to you.  Um, drop it in
the chat.  And other than that,
thank you all for your time
and I hope you all have a
good rest of your week  and
goodbye.